CASSANDRA **VELLA**

GHARGHUR, MT ↑
+356 9958 0803 ↓
c.vella@outlook.com ✓
https:/www.linkedin.com/in/cassandrav



OBJECTIVE

Over the last 5 years I have had a diverse Sales & Administrative career which has seen me undertake various roles such as relationship management, leadership and training facilitator which are just a few to name. I am highly committed to building long lasting relationships with both internal and external stakeholders and work timelessly to promote a win-win solution in all transactions. A highlight of my career was being given the opportunity to travel offshore to the Philippines in order to facilitate training of a new team. The success of this project saw the business offshore the majority of their administration roles and resulted in a reduction in staffing costs.

I am looking for a position in Sales or Administration where I can use my skills and integrate strategies to help achieve positive results.



EDUCATION

Bachelor Laws / Social Science | University of Western Sydney CURRENTLY DEFERRED

Higher School Certificate | All Saints Catholic Senior College 2012 - 2013



EXPERIENCE

Business Development Manager | Aqubix, Malta MARCH 2019 - PRESENT

- Responsible for Identifying new sales new opportunities and potential markets for penetration
- Book meetings with potential clients and demo solution either online or in person depending on location
- Extensive diary management (organizing meetings in different timezones)
- Follow up with prospective clients and assist with any enquiries
- Research prospective accounts in targeted markets, pursue leads and follow through to a successful agreement.
- Monitor and report on market and competitor activities and provide relevant reports and information to management.
- Effective management of the sales pipeline to ensure conversion
- Support and closely collaborate with CEO to implement strategies aimed at increasing revenue and customer experience
- Draft marketing campaigns for publication on social media pages and company website

- Create conference and identify sponsorship opportunities based on company budget and target market
- Attend and represent the company at local and international events as an exhibitor or delegate

National Relationship Manager | Pepper Money, Australia MARCH 2018 – MARCH 2019

- Provide a high level of support to Regional and State Managers
- Work directly with the third-party sector and Business Development Team to structure financing solutions to support their customers' requirements and objectives.
- Drive business growth through customer acquisition and quality referrals
- Proactively call Brokers to ensure they are consistently engaged and utilizing our product suite
- Proactively monitor pipeline to ensure that deals and transactions are progressing through to settlement
- Maintain an ongoing commitment to tracking leads to ensure conversion and targets are achieved
- Continually looking for ways to streamline and simplify our business through knowledge of our business goals and customers objectives.
- Act as a focal point for the Broker network in times where a reactive approach may be required i.e. escalations, decline reviews

Team Leader – Broker Support | Pepper Money, AustraliaMAY 2017 – MARCH 2018

- Responsible for driving the performance and quality of work within the Broker Support Team 10 direct reports.
- Responsible for mentoring, coaching and developing a team of Broker Support Officers to ensure performance and client experience is of the highest quality
- Conduct QA checks for temporary and permanent employees to ensure agents are meeting customer service objectives.
- Assist Business Excellence Team with internal projects such as training, risk and compliance.
- Conduct audits on all aggregators to ensure product, policy and rates are accurate for introducers.
- Run daily, weekly and monthly reports for Senior Management
- Responsible for the recruitment of new employees

Sales Support Officer | Pepper Money, Australia

APRIL 2016 – MAY 2017

- Providing support to Sales and Business Development Managers as well as Introducers to achieve desired revenue, margin and profit targets.
- Workshop scenarios with Introducers to ensure scenario meets Pepper product and credit criteria
- Use product and credit knowledge to recommend/quote products to suit customers requirements and objectives.
- Create and maintain training materials for both Sales and Credit Support teams
- Conduct training for all new starters in Sales and Credit Support (voice training + product and systems training)

- Facilitate training offshore in Pepper Manila Service Centre this included creating the training framework and materials as well as facilitating the training offshore
- Train new Business Development Managers and Relationship Managers in product and policy

Receptionist / PA | Patterson Building Group, Sydney JANUARY 2014 – APRIL 2016

- JANUART 2014 APRIL 2010
- Handle all administrative tasks such as archiving, filing, ordering supplies
- Manage multiple inboxes and manage queries and correspondence
- Screen calls and direct requests to appropriate personnel
- Extensive diary management (both personal and professional)
- Organise travel arrangements
- Responsible for organizing corporate events
- Handle all incoming and outgoing mail
- Assist Head of Marketing with tenders and other marketing campaigns
- Take meeting minutes



SKILLS

- Team Leadership
- Problem Solving
- Negotiation
- Time Management

- Project Management
- Risk Analysis
- Communication



VOLUNTEER WORK

Cerebral Pawsy Alliance | Liverpool, New South Wales 2012-2013